Allah says that permission
has been granted to those who were
oppressed to fight and then Allah says
that they were driven out of their homes
they were driven out of their homes
without any right, unjustly except that they say
our Lord is Allah subhanahu wa ta'ala
and then Allah subhanahu wa ta'ala says
immediately after that about permission
to fight, He explains the wisdom behind
that permission.
He says that the permission
is because : Had it not been that some
people defended other people
in other words strong people defended
weak people
then temples
and synagogues and churches
and mosques would be destroyed. That this is the reason
Allah subhanahu wa ta'ala gave permission for people to defend other people in order to,
in other words to defend their religion
because the verse comes down
about religious persecution
religious persecution. That these people were being persecuted for their religion.
They came to Abdullah ibn 'Umar in Sahih Bukhari
and and they said to him we want to hear
some good news
so a good Hadits
and one of them said
Allah subhanahu wa ta'ala says: ...and fight
them until there's no fitna
until there's no fitna. And Abdullah ibn 'Umar said,
"Do you know what fitna is? May your
Mother weep over you."
Do you know what fitna is? And then he said,
"Fitna for us, was being forced out of
our religion."
In other words, religious persecution. And
this is why the Prophet was given permission
permission to fight the Musyrikin (idolaters)
to stop them from forcing people to
leave the religion (Islam)
And he said, "As for what you're doing today,"
"fighting for political power, fighting for
dominion,"
"this is not what the Qur'an is talking
about." The Prophet SAW said
"If Muslims,"
"together if they meet with their two
swords," in Sahih Bukhari
"if they meet with their two swords, both of
them are in the Hellfire."
People during fitna are not called
syuhada' (martyrs). You don't call people that
You don't call people who die in fitna syuhada' (martyrs). This is
according to the Muslims
the Fuqaha', the Ulama'
In the hadits in Bukhari
There will be continued to be a group of my Ummah
that is on the truth until the the end
of time
Imam al Bukhari says,
in the same chapter, they're the people
of knowledge
Allah says about the people going out
that not everybody should go out there
should be a group that stays home, why
in order to learn the religion. And then
to warn them when they come back
to warn them what this religion is about
why we fight. What's the purpose of the
fighting
now you have in the Muslim Ummah and I
don't
you know it's not my want
to talk about politics in the in
the (khutbah) Jum'ah
because the Prophet SAW, I looked
at all
the khutbahs that were available
collected in a book and I in finding a
hotel where he talked about the
political problems at his time
all it was about rectifying the hearts
about having to quell about getting
close to a lot that's when he talked
about
but he also had time with other people
and now we're in a time of great
confusion
there's confusion we have people in this
country going
overseas is hard to believe but there's
people going
to join up to join the heat up for we
have people in England going to join the
key to
people it from Muslim countries now
going
we there's a young tell me boy going
from reality was first your religious
student goes online
so come join the kidnapper here's the
Calif right and so they go
is a madness complete insanity is
unbelievable
the province allies adam said how long
will you be like
mantle what are you hearing him say
moments of mantle like what are you
without as much as you for no intellect
what are you
either many did you know calm when your
religion becomes confused
well so he could email column and
bloodshed is everywhere
what the heart is enough and then you
have luxury on the other hand you've got
all these people
in indulging in their luxuries shuttle
yet
and you building tall building what are
you like what what are you
mount on so
if you look at these tires were like his
permission
to fight permission was granted it's a
isn't it's all Rossa finding is not
something desirable
the province also lightness and I'm
sentence I hid behind a letter to men
only part I do
don't desire to meet the enemy don't
desire that this is a sickness in the
heart
people that desire to go is a sickness
in the heart inside and Behati
in the chapter which is called the fifth
ability to move to Bible happy bob
fits into that comes like waves
is one after another is one after
another incomes Lightwave
it says that caught up in that house
upset
can use the gonna so how bout can use
that have gone in yet another
through we are getting their place they
used to recite yeah
early poetry when the fits in would come
they would recite
people what was what they would recite
Harbaugh automatic or 30 attend
tests are at the scene that he had the
collegian gillooly
had to either steffi other was shocked
but there are more ha well let the Jews
and
later that actually they would recite
the poem to remind each other
the fifth not when it first appears it
appears like a decked out beautiful
woman
attracting every young ignoramus every
young ignoramus
until the conflagration happens
war breaks out and then they see it for
what it is an old hag no longer
desirable
nobody wants it this is the disease
above
%uh young men the proposal I sent
there's a chapter called
Hakone MITI adderall they met in super
hot
the destruction of my own at the hands
of stupid young boys
stupid young boy these people are
playing with fire
and this fire could break out a
conflagration you know what once you get
what you get
a a bonfire hand you have dry grass
everywhere
it takes over even the firemen here they
can put out these fires
they have all the technology in the
world once you start a fire
you know how hard it is to put out a
forest fire when it's dry
and what do you think that is fitna
is is fire the test goal that's the
meaning of that on a
out on their you afternoon on the fire
there the in in the Hellfire
other night you've turned on who of
Internet to comb
taste your fitness you want fitna Google
fanatical
taste it but nobody wants to
nobody was suppose he will not let
that's the first thing the people
knowledge have no voice anymore
is is all the young boys out there on
on Google that that's who now rules is
religion
young boys not people that will spend
twenty years to study the religion
to look at what the football has it now
is is young boys
this is who runs our religion this is
what gives the fat one now
and I don't know when they speak they
sell
oh no muscle fun you can go to the
desert
a the Sahara thirst also a mother
not many left but there's still some
they've never gone inside a palace that
never spoken to anybody in political
power
and you ask them what they think what's
the ruling of God in His people that
spent 30 years
studying FIP mastering a tradition
mastering the Arabic language
now you have people we've got
crucifixion because these idiots read
the Koran
there is a will there is right there in
the koran crucified people
you open up the koran 44
for everybody in sale here does anybody
can read the Koran I know Arabic
I have a four year degree from
Baghdad University Imam shafii studies
17 years
these people didn't speak about the
religion
the Sahaba were afraid to say things
they were afraid to speak
no one after that
%uh says under the name it can no longer
are they accomplish a lot
those who when we give them time keenan
the earth what do they do
they establish prayer Latos ECA and they
take your poor people
well when my only one hot lemon curd
well in the apt a bit more
and they they then join good and the for
been what's wrong
the Prophet said how will you be when
the mother of his mall cop
and the more cars model how will you be
what people will see
are wrong thing as a good thing and OC
a good thing as a wrong thing how you be
one
when they'll see compassion is weakness
mercy as weakness
the problems lie some was a merciful
percent
101 need inside and Behati one
when how did the bill will need actually
had prisoners and
and and they were they were so confused
they couldn't speak
properly and that he had them killed
some other
men that were within reviews to kill
them because no party must look at the
mercy of the heart
they refused to kill to prisoners is
that we're not going to do that when
they got back to the province allies and
they told the proper what happened
that he killed the prisoners the Prophet
turn immediately to the camera
raises hands are all law I'm completely
innocent what caught it is done
I'm completely innocent what colin has
done
because why you're putting one on FB
Muskingum wait till what assira
they feed out above got the the orphan
the the the indigent the poor people and
the Prisoner
the proper flies into characters
prisoners Hwy was the best in people
even two hundred years ago in this
country two hundred years ago benjamin
Franklin
can ride in his autobiography ever since
hard it was rebuked
by Mohammed muslims have always treated
their prisoners well
what now on chopping off heads
a people that go there too to actually
inform people about the atrocities
that are taking place this is this is
how you this is how you treat prisoners
and then it's all his vengeance there's
nothing to do with Islam
people have nothing to do with Islam and
also
right here they have nothing to do with
Islam
these people have nothing to do with
this religion
now they're using these black flags
because there's had these about the
black flags coming from
Afghanistan at towards the end of time
but they don't know that there's
actually two different
black flag those black flags have been
about us but then there's another group
a black flags
that we were warned against say not only
says and I have you been to be a part in
Rd the item a riotous sued says the
monarch what are to have any cool
a vehicle module comm stayed put why
because it's it now
stay put what do you do there in 15 you
do what the Prophet SAW i said im set
when they think that comes you stay in
your house
cool Henderson at nasa bait you don't go
out
the proposal i said im settle bad tooth
unfit sanity can he get at the ITA
that doing a bad during fitness is like
making him the right to me
because his religion is not a religion
of it now and civil strife
persecution these years eighties have
been living there for centuries
the Christians this is a testimony to
the beauty of our religion
that the Christian church Syria and Iraq
for centuries live with their church is
inviolable
they could worship God
in their churches and they didn't they
weren't afraid of the muslims
and now they're running they're fleeing
saying that I the said the only other
almond Board I thought now you
the hotel then you will see these weak
insignificant people
got to tell you about a insignificant
people
insignificant people these are not
notables
they have no learning there's no
scholars amongst them
insignificant people Google home
consumer ed hardy
their hearts are like pieces are iron
entering why are they are up for to what
Obama to
other do we have they have no mercy with
their enemies and the Prophet SAW II
some said Monday a ham radio ham
even this poor mother asking for her
child
to be and let me say something just
predicate is here
I'm not exonerating these
neo-conservatives the open this door
alright I'm not exonerating
what this country did to the iraqi
people
alright who opened the door for
I'm not exonerating them some I'm not
talking but I'm dealing with what we've
got right now
that happen now we have another
situation we can play the blame game cuz
that's it pleases favorite game
that is his favorite game did not wait
any
that we handle much money passing police
are our religion is Adam and his
them he
he said but I'm not listen to him say it
please make me do it
right cuz also my buddies he he
said in you know clinton also keen on
giving sincere I think believe them
there they were like children they were
innocent they believe the police
and they fell he didn't say only please
he swore an oath we never thought he'd
lie
they didn't play in a bit that's why his
honey for that's why Adams honey because
he didn't do what the police did
it please blames got you led me astray
so you can't blame
America you can blame Israel but if you
if you want to get to the metaphysical
level then we have to do with our sins
how why did they come but just looking
at a Dr
at 9am that Lana we sent them are
servants those with the Babylonian they
were the people
hop if they were set to ben is right
here why
because benny is what I had deviated
from the path and so got sent them
servants that would going to their
houses
take their women kill their men why
because Committee on the tomato majority
that will have you doing %uh
myeloma is a is a is is a owner that has
reimer
because all other punishment is here in
this world then what are the safest soon
was it as you want but I it you look at
the earthquakes in the Muslim world
we have earthquakes 10,000 people die
ever earthquake killed three people died
this this is what I was it that
that we're going to the proper size M
said we will have fit in
when we deviate there yet him but he
knew how did when I remember he
until she wanted to let them be warm if
you go against
the mess the messenger if you would go
against his guidance
the province said that that when they
gave battle
and that soon as I i'm not that you
don't go against the soap on
the Prophet SAW license so that people
know they so those are these they're
just put there by
people that wanted to calm people down
in so
a Bihari none of these have better sound
none other things the economist said for
centuries
now of course in this in lighten age
we're going to reinterpret
the whole religion this revolutionary
age well we get rid of all these
evil doers and the pure a the pure
owner is gonna come
what is this what happened
this is this is a state but see they
have hearts like iron
who must have a doler as what is that
must have a doler
the other people a doler that's their
name
go to they contacted in the Arab world
know that Islamiyah
ride they're the people a donor I wasn't
even a word the Arab used other than
just
to rupaul something to get typical a.m.
would no doubt will happen as they can
use it for state
at that time well have a donor level
rather than what I meet up
they will not have any covenant you
can't trust them with anything that they
say
you don't have that happen is a man and
he
they call to the truth but they're not
from the people at the truth why because
in the hadith the Prophet SAW light
isn't
whenever they purr people rising but Eve
also have a hearty
her they've up gonna be a man the people
are asking about good he wanted to ask
about
shower out of fear that he might see it
he said not a law
could not see yediyat in which are for
John alone to have a higher
we were in jabaliya and char and then
got brought this
this good to us is there any bad after
this good he said no
and then he said is Ernie good after
that bad he said now will be the hon
yes but it it's going to be cloudy it
will have the same purity
and he said map motherhood only also a
lot what what's the cloudiness
he said Oman yeah I don't have any had
the
that any woman would talk to you people
will guide
with other than my guidance you will
know some things in your reject other
things
and then he said is there even after
that good he said now
due at noon a bourbon mom
man a job a home other fool see those
who
their their collars on the doors of the
hell
if you answer them if you respond to
their call
you'll be flown into the hell how they
visit civil none I also a law
describe them for us so we'll know them
home engine bettina
the arabs they're like I first mentioned
that you know they look like us
yet again I wanna be a singer Tina
they'll
quote the Koran
no quota had the those are the problem
lies in describe him
them and then he said not
gave it up not only are also what what
do you command me to do at that time
he said doesn't gym at NYC mean way my
mom
be with the genera and the Imam when you
can no longer my daughter is not what if
there's no drama
and no ima factors attitude can set up a
cool app
what I want to help but be all city
should get in had tell you dedicated
mode want I love that
so he had he said avoid all those sex
even if you have to cling to the root of
a tree with your
T until death comes to you and your
on he didn't say are never done to Pima
ok enough haha the far too cute idea
then say you have to
established that he die for but these
people they don't study
there how large and and in this media
here's calling them
Sunnis because they're killing Shia
they're not sonny's
these are Sunnis a similar Gemma these
are now in police
very often had a welfare and huh
I didn't but Hannah one group was guided
and another group honey him about that
but the idea but a
in the how do you then he says a small
Roman Cucina
this are you know them and if you don't
think these are accurate description
her they've %uh said the Prophet got up
in a hot but
and he spoke to hold a he said every
single fit that would happen until the
end of time
he described the leaders he told us
their names he told us what would happen
and he said some others could remember
and other us couldn't
every single fitna so don't think these
things were mention
a small home a corner
their names are album so and so on up
also on cell
they don't go by their real names us
moment gonna when this petaluma cora
and the and they there they go back to
towns places they don't go to try
because the air
go by tried these people know they go by
places a buck daddy
and body
a jew a she all these all these names
that their towns that they're from
leaving and mostly and 100 be
they go back to places this what the
private license because it has had a
rough at and people can say it's a week
senate
sounds pretty sound to me what's your
own home their hard earned cash or
tourney sup they have long hair
wearing it like women look at all the
pictures that these guys
with the long hair cuz
it's not that the problem lies in didn't
have long hair but it's no longer
fashionable in the Arab world
ever know where their their hair long so
that's a sign
that you know them their hairs long
had to have that he will be no they
don't those are fightin months each
other
that's the nature there's another
troubling had that the proposal i said
im said such a cool fits attuned to show
them
010 her labels
yen it begins with children playing
in Dera and then he said
that it'll just be after that one-fifth
after another column a second a fit in
at one has yet to turn it into a
every time the calm down in one place it
starts up somewhere else in this
either how was it the riot the suit if
you see the black flags
they know what I have it's not it begins
with a fit in a
what was upheld by Lana and
and and the midst of it is delusion miss
guidance
error what he had a call from
and ends with atheism this was gonna
happen people
people start losing their faith what
happened to the europeans they had world
war 1&2 was enough for them they don't
believe in God in with a word
profoundly religious civilization with
all the churches they built people get
people can take it that so much
where's got the question is not where is
God is where are we
that's the question laser on the other
hand he's not as about what he did but
we're going to ask about what we did
why are we following the guidelines that
the Prophet a lot incident
and in this howdy that mike foale
relates
this is Maddie what he'd done it at that
cuz they
most of these they thought had to do
with the Abbasid but then he said share
your own party they split my own a
well best known he have a cell at and
they put black clothes on them
and that's only other not may God put
clothes a fire on them
these people are how outage
they're killing moslems that they
they've
every single criteria and don't be
fooled by their piety
don't be fooled by their piety cuz the
province allied isms
soda and also out to him to you're also
a time when you see them pray
you'll consider your prayer
insignificant when the CM him
that people want to see amacom but he
said
yep crawler koran well let the dollar
hand ideal
they'll recite the Koran it won't go
past that brought the Roma said I mean
they won't understand it
they don't because they don't have the
tools you can understand the koran
without the tools
they won't understand and many said %um
upon a minute then so have a hottie
yarmulke limited income a young man who
puts out more memorabilia
they will leave this religion like it a
row
shot out of a bowl and
an injury why in a Bihari it says yeah
crucial CEO Matti and then the row he
says Mark column in her
there will come out amongst my Oma and
he didn't say from it
because they're not from him these
people are not from the Prophet SAW II
sent they have nothing to do
with the man who was sent as a mercy for
all the world and the fact that they're
in any way shape
or form associated with this religion is
a great tragedy
most homes in this country have a big
responsibility to get out there
educate people because these people are
watching these newscast and maybe there
is some
other agencies about I don't know
because this this the age if it's in Sol
confusion
so the problems lie some said but as far
as i'm concerned. I'm not confused
I'm not confuse
if you're confused and study this
religion
and if you think this has
anything to do with the truth you
definitely haven't studied this religion
because these people are sheltering
is plain and some and an undeniably
there's
a these a but yet you the sacrificial
lambs
like this 18-year-old boy who left three
Al
who's been brainwashed to think that
this religions about hating other people
you know because unfortunately have
certain
sects in Islam now that teach that all
cool far are bad
even on the peron clearly states that
among them are good people
amongst them were trustworthy people
ron is a nuance book it's not a
simplistic book is not a black-and-white
world
and then Eurasian a min inmate we have
three inmates minute hi
front cover comes demand from the man
comes call for that were fluid by nature
humans are fluid
people are in one state one day there in
another state the next day
Buffalo
locally helpful
handle assault Wilson wanna see them
lani Wilson unfortunately there's not
many
a scholars left in our own a there
really isn't
but the few that are left they all agree
they all say the same things that
whether they were
trained in in Afghanistan or Mauritania
or Malaysia or Egypt or iraq
if they were trade in the senate
tradition they all say the same thing
they don't disagree the others amazing
thing about this religion but
the sex outside they disagree they have
different opinions
and that doesn't mean that the scholars
don't differ among them but about
certain things
they're they're in agreement about and
one of them
is that fitna is worse than
then killing fitness were thinkin koran
and fit in a a couple min a party
civil strife is worse than killing
itself just the fact that humans are
filled with strike because she about us
that's what he wants to reduce us
he wants to prove that that the Angels
in their question to God are you gonna
place in the earth
those who corrupt and shed blood doesn't
shed blood that's what they ask is it
that this what they can do the profit so
i said im said you have wiggle room with
your Lord
as long as you don't shed blood the
Koran says if you kill a believer
with her and made a judges I hope your
your your reward is Dan
that's faster or killing a believer
and and
and why had they have rights people have
rights these people have rights
the Syrian Christians the the Syrian
to all the people have rights then why
hadn't they're supposed to be protected
and the she are Muslims they're they're
not go far
they're muslims just because he's a Shia
doesn't give anybody a ride to
to to kill him or do anything but these
people don't care we
I'm not a man in Turkey who was a Knox
money from had a
yeah welt on his back
from the torture that they did with him
top why because he was the man
in a mesh did that where they did the
car in a group
that's why he was tortured and they were
gonna kill 'em he escaped they had a
raid on
and and a bomb fell and he got out and
he fled to Turkey we met him i sad lunch
with them
that doesn't I people were dealing with
and then they've got all the women
covered from head to toe
there's not enough new card is not a
for that's an opinion on other minority
of the oklahoma
the majority don't say the face is not
considered our but they force
because they only one opinion my opinion
one religion my religion
what I say is the only way to understand
this religion so
work at work we're gonna have to do with
this year because it all started up
again
is all started up again and
don't think you can be comfortable in
your homes really I'm telling you
I'm telling do not think that you can be
comfortable in your home
because we're we're in a very precarious
situation the first with these mosques
thank God we've got some social order
here so shorter breaks down
people get fed up you know the Arab say
watch out for a the Haleem if he gets
angry
people that don't get angry quickly when
they get angry
watch out and now it's starting over
again
there they're gonna start bombing in
again most invariably
innocent Muslims were killed in the sink
and it just keeps this cycle the
violence going
doesn't stop because these people have
they don't know what to do all they know
is to kill
that's all they're just like these group
over here that's all they know in the
how deep they say their showers omit
omits kill kill that's all they know
so you know we have to do with it but
muslims
we need to wake up we need to have the C
group we need
people need to support the the group
that are out there
empower them they need to be doing more
work
I mean I'm doing is 10 years I feel like
I
you know I I just think I would all
those places all those talks all those
things and it's just
we're back to square one were actually
worth as far as I can tell
this is worse than before 9/11 even my
father who know
just mom I went on to some for thirty
years his psych is this
Islam you know that cutting off heads I
guess it's in the koran
so back to square one thirty years a
dour you know
the few I think they're gonna have an
excuse on your cam all these people
as a core demand as I what's our excuse
promise i said im
you know he said that the the
all the fitnah comes from the who demand
o'mara does work comes from
their own a man they don't speak out
they don't
or they or they sell their Dean right
and then the Omaha that you know but
then also these these political
these people that turned responding to a
political ideology get power
you have to blame them as well we're
going to start the blame game
long list but in the end we
we have to say that well known for sana
men entered havana I
what I've read in a that have not been a
conundrum in a constant you don't have
mercy on us for give up we're gonna be
from the losers
so this in the end we have to call a lot
in fact
the fitnah in in the hadeeth the
proposal i said im said
that the only one that we say from that
is the one that makes the diana
other a drowning man you have to make
the two-hour
a meant that do at a hundred the battery
the one that makes land you mean her in
a min dad do adequate body
the they won't have salvation and as you
make the dough out a drowning man
in in the ocean so this is what we're up
against
but not I i feel compelled to talk about
this
I feel compelled to you know we have
some young people that
think somehow this has anything to do
with Islam
you need to educate these young people
yeah young people filled with zeal they
want to do something
and
and they're fed up with seeing
palestinians sacred
muslims massacred nobody cares they
don't care here
they talked the talk about the
Christians in Iraq what about all the
Muslims
for more motions have suffered at the
hands these people that
than Chris they will talk about the most
Muslim the we don't mean anything
and that's that's the other half the
equation is that they
they see that there's no mercy in the
hearts up these people
so they feel compelled to show no mercy
but does not our religion does another
religion
that's not our religion our profits I
sent did not
a he lay later to see if the same he
didn't repel
a wrong with another wrong that can but
has an A
and he said follow up a bad thing with a
good thing temple her
and it will obliterate it that's does
his religion
but does a hard religion is a lot easier
to get angry
lot more difficult to to do that along
offered an hour
from north to abandon the outlaw ya
hamara minotaur
camera mean along a with the judge in
Chandler
I'm in home he had to him long bar had
to him along with a gym a broader
something much koran
with them foreign what do into upon him
said to me on me
Aloma John shelhah bar Mecca to
minal Olbia women and Nick about women
had it on rather than the team to show
that he had
%um along much of the comb were at home
are so hot yeah
more me had to him alarm a min of the
opening Iowa Minnesota and Iowa that in
Alhambra
mean a call from a rocky mean a long
enough they said in that heat up with a
sinner
not lace alone up to the right now you
add his own a telephone Adina
along a min along on the non-muslim mean
along I'm in north east across the north
to share
with Libya oh he must sort of a rock of
the Afghanistan officials channel see
for not being we'll see a she cashmere
with a young man
was the honey open market with a desire
for you had american wheat turkey a
along a minute
a truck milk a woman and marker women a
shower
law llamame in Malaysian along I'm an
old on Alhambra
me not and that in the tournament in the
shade
land ownership as usual monetary
forgetting that we have nothing
ya la nothing we only have you that's
all we have we have nothing
we only have use hand and that the guy
we believe in you
well known that I love him but also a
lot a field on our home now
%uh the the new to shut up Yuma to
nothing could make a
this informers everywhere yellow your
profit warned us
and we didn't miss India's advice that
will have to be mad a superwoman
don't take us to account for what these
fools a month
as do law
a long look for an hour note about any
camera
in the in the couple who called clock in
the loma it could use under United maybe
a under the nominal sum do it.
something with this team along slowly on
a CD
happy him along our home
Tim along a ham to have you
tool her all matter most of oil
no matter how mad alone hmmm
along not home on the to Mohamed Salah
dissident
like to learn to sew by hand aka not
gonna
person in them up for dinner with on
Leno Conan ha sitting alone from an hour
providing in the light call him a liar
model but a deal would essentially to
either portable 100 bash at 11 could
work but here at the Connecticut to the
cool
welcome also like the politically some